爸
Hey, Pop.
凱文·安德伍德
好久不見啊
Been a while, hasn't it?
看到車隊駛過來了嗎
Did you see that motorcade roll up?
這是首次有美國總統
It's the first time that the President of the United States
來到加夫尼
has visited Gaffney.
你能相信嗎
Can you believe it?
如果有的選  我也不會來
Oh, I wouldn't be here if I had a choice.
但我現在得做這種事了
But I have to do these sort of things now.
讓我顯得更有人情味
Makes me seem more human.
做總統就得有點人情味
And you have to be a little human when you're the president.
他都沒錢給自己買墓碑
He couldn't even afford to pay for his own gravestone.
我用自己桑蒂諾軍事學院的獎學金買的
I paid for it out of my own scholarship money from The Sentinel.
他葬禮那天只有我去了
Nobody showed up for his funeral except me.
我母親都沒去
Not even my mother.
但我要告訴你  爸
But I'll tell you this, though, Pop:
等我下葬的時候  絕不會是葬在自家後院
when they bury me, it won't be in my backyard.
等人們前來弔唁的時候
And when they come to pay their respects,
他們得排隊
they'll have to wait in line.
你該讓我們在墓地拍張照
You should let us take a photo at the grave.
他想要點隱私  他可是在給父親掃墓啊
He wants privacy. The man's honoring his father, for God's sakes.
翻譯   草草
翻譯   國士章魚X
翻譯   肉鬆富士
翻譯   癢癢
翻譯   魚小姐啦
時間軸   aaaBao
後期   餓得慌
顧問   老杜
鳴謝   忙成狗的網飛
鳴謝   阿小小海
特效   草草
校對   草草
總監   草草
■
本字幕由 YYeTs 人人影視 原創翻譯
[WEB&BD版美劇字幕精編者]再加工製成
本人由衷感謝原譯作者的無私奉獻  並保留譯作者的信息
如需其它劇集字幕  請登陸新浪微博（http://weibo.com/MJZM100）
或發郵件索取 lj20090303@163.com
紙牌屋
第三季  第一集
這是你要的信息
Here's the info you were looking for.
我們把那個安排在了下週二早上10點
And we have that scheduled for next Tuesday at 10 a.m.
沒問題吧
That's still good for you, right?
很好  我會確認的
Excellent. I'll confirm it.
抱歉
Excuse me.
什麼事  先生
Yes, sir?
是  先生
Yes, sir.
總統可以見你了
The president is ready to see you now.
天吶
Jesus.
我傷心欲絕
I'm devastated.
我愛他如子
I love this man as if he were my son.
他是個鬥士  我相信他能挺過來
Now, he's a fighter, and I'm sure that he'll pull through.
我們都為他祈禱
Our prayers are with him.
"...安德伍德總統昨日在一場新聞發佈會上如是說
"...said President Underwood during a press conference yesterday.
馬里蘭州警方
The Maryland State Police
和聯邦有關部門尚未找到
and Federal authorities have yet to locate
斯坦普先生的車或提出任何嫌疑人"
Mr. Stamper's car or name any suspects."
還想聽嗎  弟弟
You want more of this, brother?
或許聽聽體育版吧
Or maybe the sports page?
"世界職業棒球大賽第六場比賽
"Game Six of the World Series
連續13局未得分
went scoreless for 13 innings
緊接著又因大雨延遲
before a rain delay
使這個已具有史詩性的夜晚
that turned an already epic evening
足以載入史冊"
into one for the history books."
心思與你同在
弗蘭克
克萊爾
美國總統
第一夫人
31號病房需要醫生
We need a doctor in room three-one.
道格拉斯
Douglas?
能聽到嗎
Can you hear me?
如果能聽到眨下眼睛
I want you to blink if you can hear me.
再來
Again.
我是蘭吉維尼醫生
My name is Dr. Lanjwani.
總統辦公室要求我親自看護你
The president's office asked me to look after you personally.
你能得到最好的護理  好嗎
You're getting the very best of care, okay?
道格拉斯  如果你能感覺到  就眨眼睛
Douglas, I want you to blink if you can feel this.
很好  很好
Good. Good.
這樣呢
How about this?
好的  很好
Okay. Excellent.
這樣呢
And this?
這裏呢
How about here?
放鬆
Relax.
放鬆  早期階段這很正常
Relax. Perfectly normal at this early stage.
放鬆
Relax.
很好
That's good.
好的  休息吧
Okay. Get some rest.
你是不是要傷害我
Are you gonna hurt me?
你讓我幹什麼都行  求你別傷害我
I will do whatever you want, please just don't hurt me.
-疼嗎  -有點
- Does that hurt? - A little.
好了  我們開始吧  握拳
All right, let's go ahead. Try and make a fist for me.
-雷米  -什麼
- Remy. - What's that?
雷米·丹頓  他在嗎
Remy Danton. Was he here?
他來過  來看你怎麼樣了
He was. Just checking on your progress.
來  握個拳
Go ahead, make that fist for me.
獅子
Lion.
犀牛
Rhinoceros.
-駱駝  -很好
- Camel. - Good.
魯道夫的鼻子什麼顏色
What color is Rudolph's nose?
-魯道夫  -馴鹿
- Rudolph? - Reindeer.
紅色
Red.
是紅色的
It's red.
美國總統
The President of the United States?
道格拉斯
Douglas?
美國總統是誰
Who is the President of the United States?
弗蘭克·安德伍德
Frank Underwood.
-今年是哪年  -2014年
- What year are we in? - 2014.
幾月份
What month is it?
12月
It's December.
我得回去工作
I have to get back to work.
道格拉斯  聽我說
Douglas. Listen to me.
你遭受了有創骨折...
You suffered a compound fracture--
我知道我什麼毛病
I know what I fucking suffered!
你好好聽我說
I need you to hear me this time.
你左額皮質遭到了損傷
There was damage to your left frontal cortex.
你的運動技能將有退化
Your motor skills will be a struggle.
你將情緒多變
Your emotions will be unpredictable.
前面的路很長  我們不能心急
There's a long road ahead, and we can't rush it.
-我們稍後做測試吧  -不
- Let's do the test later. - No.
現在就做完
We'll finish it now.
你母親叫什麼
What was your mother's name?
她年輕漂亮
She was young and beautiful.
雅各在她照看羊喝水時愛上了她
Jacob fell in love with her while she was watering a lamb, and...
他做了七年的工
she became his wife after he worked seven years
才終於娶到她
to earn her hand in marriage.
推  腳跟向我手裏使勁
Push back. Heel into my hand.
呼吸
Breathe.
歸位  深呼吸  準備好了嗎
Back up. Deep breath. Ready?
推  用力
Push. Push.
道格
Doug.
集中注意
Focus.
我今天遞交國會的報告
The report I submit to Congress today
所包含的證據
includes evidence that
通常足以展開刑事檢控
would normally warrant criminal prosecution,
但鑒於總統特赦
but the Justice Department won't pursue charges
司法部不會提出起訴
in accordance with the presidential pardons.
我很感激鄧巴女士及其團隊
I'm grateful for the hard work Ms. Dunbar and her team
對此次調查的盡心盡力
have dedicated to their investigation.
作為回應  我將組建跨黨派委員會
In response, I'll be forming a bipartisan commission
研究競選籌款改革  以確保歷史不再重演
to examine campaign finance reform so history does not repeat itself,
也讓我們國家癒合傷口
and so that our nation can heal from these wounds.
我有培根芝士和普通的  你要哪種
I got bacon-cheese and regular. Which one you want?
等等
Just a minute.
還記得你以前從不吃
Remember when you'd never eat a burger
沒有培根的漢堡嗎
if it didn't have bacon on it?
爸會發火
Dad would get so pissed
因為他討厭烤培根油的味兒
because he hated the smell of bacon grease on the grill.
我在聽呢  加裏
I'm trying to listen, Gary.
總統也沒辦法  就讓他去死[燒]吧
The president's hands are tied. Might as well let him burn.
改革不止需要一個委員會
他們在準備棉花糖了
They're getting their marshmallows ready.
看看安德伍德的支持率
Look at Underwood's approval rating.
比沃克辭職之前的還糟
It's worse than Walker's before he resigned.
要從那個坑裏爬出來  會很不容易
That's a deep, deep hole to climb out of.
共和黨會得意一陣了
The Republicans are gonna have their fun for a while.
普選時有很多可以拿來打擊他的東西
Plenty to hammer him on in the general.
而且他們一心想傷人見血
And they're out for blood.
教育和福利改革他們都輸得很慘
They lost big on education and entitlement reform.
還有  如果那些關於
And if the rumors
《美國就業法案》的傳言是真...
about America Works are true...
這計劃對左派太右
For the left, that's just too far to the right
對右派太左
and for the right, it's too far to the left.
他們需要我回去
They need me back.
哪裏  白宮嗎
Where? The White House?
我們得扭轉局勢  開始為2016造聲勢
We got to turn the corner, start ramping up for 2016.
他或許能扭轉乾坤呢
He might turn this around.
你不是真覺得他會贏吧
You don't really think he's gonna win, do you?
他經驗豐富  安德伍德有很多...
The guy's experienced. Underwood has a lot...
他會恢復的
He'll recover.
他是個幕後推手
He's a behind-the-scenes guy.
他在聚光燈下不自在
He's not comfortable in the spotlight.
不如你先恢復吧
How about you recover first?
...假意熱情  親吻嬰兒
...glad-handing and kissing babies.
如果這證明了什麼  就是這18個月會很漫長
This is gonna be a long 18 months if this proves any indication.
會許下一堆空頭承諾
It can be a lot of chest-thumping
但卻毫無建樹
but nothing really getting done.
解憂靈有助緩解抑鬱癥
The Xybenetrin will help with depression.
丁螺環酮是治療焦慮的  給你
The buspirone is for anxiety. Here you go.
我想給你開點止疼藥  但鑒於你的...
I'd like to prescribe you something for the pain, but with your...
所有有癮史的病人...
Well, any patient with a history of addictive behavior--
我懂  沒事
I know. It's fine.
疼我撐得住
I can handle the pain.
他看上去好多了
He looks a lot better.
不  他還在睡呢
No, he's still asleep.
我得掛了
I have to go.
好
Okay.
打擾你了嗎
Is this a bad time?
沒有  沒事
No. It's fine.
就是沒人告訴我你要來
No, it's just no one told me you were coming.
弗蘭西斯要我代好
Francis sends his love.
他很想親自來  但是媒體...
He would visit himself, but with the media...
不  我懂
No, I understand.
他之前來過的  那時...
He did come before, when...
-我們倆都來過  -我知道
- Both of us. - I know.
我看到花了  謝謝
I saw the flowers. Thank you.
-你看上去挺好  -我在好起來了
- You look well. - I'm getting there.
我只想好起來  好回去工作
I just want to get better so I can get back to work.
我們都盼著呢
We're looking forward to that.
我們真是需要一切幫助
We can use all the help we can get, actually.
嗯  我一直在看新聞
Yeah. Been watching the news.
弗蘭西斯  他真是無計可施了  共和黨...
Francis, he's at his wit's end. The Republicans...
不肯給他一張他能簽的法案
won't send him a single bill he can sign.
-民主黨也好不到哪去  -鮑勃·博奇
- And the Democrats aren't much better. - Bob Birch?
瞎子給蠢貨帶路
Blind leading the stupid.
雷米幹得還好嗎
How's Remy working out?
我們更希望是你在  但他還不錯
Well, we'd much rather have you there, but he's doing a fine job.
道格  你...記得什麼嗎
Doug, do you... recall anything?
-關於事發經過  -怎麼
- About what happened? - Why?
警察有什麼發現嗎
Did the police find something?
據我們所知是沒有
Not that we're aware of.
我們叫他們暫時不要訊問你
And we've asked them to hold off questioning you
直到你感覺好一些
until you're feeling more like yourself.
瑞秋  她...
Rachel, she...
我不記得了
I don't remember.
不  你記得
Yes, you do.
是劫車
A carjacking.
-是個男人  -什麼樣的男人
- A man. - What sort of man?
那部分記不清了
That part's fuzzy.
那就可能是任何人了  誰都可能
It could be anyone, then. Any man.
是啊  誰都可能
Yeah. Any man.
他被嚇跑了嗎
And he got frightened?
我去追他  然後就記不得了
I chased him and that's all.
知道她在哪嗎
Any idea where she is?
不知道
No.
我們一定得找到她
Because it's important that we find her.
我真不知道
I really don't know.
真的
That's the truth.
你把這些都告訴警察
I want you to tell all of this to the police,
你跟我說的原話
exactly what you told me,
關於劫車  那個男人  別提她
about the carjacking and the man. Nothing about her.
知道了
I got it.
你如果需要什麼  或記起了什麼...
If you need anything, or remember anything...
-見到你真好  -你也是
- It's good to see you. - You, too.
緊急
很好  再來  向上向前  很好
That's good. One more time. Up and forward. That's good.
很好  呼吸
Excellent. Breathe.
很好
Good.
很好  很好
Good. Good.
好了
Okay.
試試這個  你做得很好
Let's try this one. You're doing a great job.
繼續呼吸  很好
Keep breathing. Good.
很好  道格
Good job, Doug.
好的  向前來  你行的
Okay. Moving forward. You got it.
很好  很好
Great. Great job.
繼續
Keep going.
很好  呼吸
Good. Breathe.
很好  不錯
Excellent. Good.
再來一個
One more.
很好
Great job.
再來一次  就好了  準備好了嗎
One more time. It's almost done. Ready?
保持呼吸
Keep breathing.
只記得他的聲音  他說"下車"
Just his voice. He said, "Get out of the car."
能描述一下他的聲音嗎
Anything you can say about the voice?
形容下口音  咬字  音調高低
Was it, uh... Accent? Lisp? High? Low?
深沉
Deep.
就記得這些了
That's all I remember.
然後我鳴了笛
Then I laid on the horn. I...
我記得他跑了
I remember him running.
很模糊  我下了車
Like a blur, I got out.
去追他
I chased him.
我也不確定  我一定...
I'm not sure. I must have...
你去馬里蘭州那裏做什麼
What were you doing in that part of Maryland?
斯坦普先生
Mr. Stamper?
先生  你去馬里蘭州那裏做什麼
Sir. What were you doing in that part of Maryland?
我有時候會開車思考
I drive sometimes to think.
當時工作上有很多事
There was a lot on my mind with work.
我只是開車清理思緒
I drive to clear my head.
你們找到車了嗎
Have you found the car?
我們目前只有你剛剛提供的信息
We don't have anything other than what you just told us.
你的情緒最近如何  有過情緒爆發嗎
How's your mood been? Any episodes?
沒有  藥物很好使
No. The meds are working.
你只是跟我說好聽的嗎
You just telling me what I want to hear?
不是  我感覺不錯
No. I feel good.
好
Okay.
我今天就批准你出院
I'm gonna sign your release today.
但你一開始一定別太急躁
But it's important you take it easy at first.
一切都會變得難很多
Everything's gonna be much harder in general.
我知道
I know.
有人能照顧你嗎
Do you have someone who can look after you?
有  我哥哥加裏從俄亥俄州過來了
Yeah. My brother Gary's in from Ohio.
很好  他能待多久
Good. How long is he here for?
-能待一陣吧  -好的  很好
- A while, I guess. - Okay, great.
你一定要去參加互助會
It's important you go to your meetings.
繼續保持不沾酒
Stay on top of your sobriety.
拿著這個  用來注射給你開的類固醇
Take this. It's for the steroids I prescribed you.
每週一次  一針打在右腿大腿上
It's one shot into the right thigh, once a week.
護士...
The nurse, she...
-她教過我了  -好
- She showed me how. - Okay.
歡迎回家
你做的嗎
You do this?
不  不是我
No, it wasn't me.
我們找人打掃了
覺得該讓你回到整潔的家中
冰箱裏有足夠吃的
弗蘭克和克萊爾
我跟我上司談過了
I talked to my boss.
你過渡期間  我可以
I can stick around for another couple of weeks
再留兩周
while you transition back.
你該回你家人那裏
You should get back to your family.
沒事  薩拉不介意
Nah... Sarah's fine with it.
孩子們也是
The kids are, too.
加裏  我們都十年沒怎麼通話了
Gary, we've hardly spoken in ten years.
你已經做了很多了
You've already gone above and beyond.
好吧  你要我走嗎
All right. You want me to go?
我沒事了
I'm fine.
多謝你做的一切
Thanks for everything.
好吧
Okay.
有事打給我  我立刻坐飛機過來
I mean, I'm just a phone call and a plane ticket away.
一路順風
Safe travels.
保重
Take care.
加裏
Hey, Gary, I...
給我寄點孩子的照片來
Send me some pictures of the kids.
嗯  好
Yeah, I will.
我欣賞你的一點
But one of the things I admire about you
是在華盛頓特區
is that in Washington, DC,
效率這麼低的地方  你總能辦成事
which is so gridlocked, you get things done.
據我所知  你有一項新的法案
And I understand you've got, um, a new piece of legislation,
你要推出一項重要的新法案  是什麼
a major new initiative you're rolling out. What is it?
沒錯
That is correct.
是一項新就業計劃  《美國就業法案》
It's a new jobs program that we're calling America Works.
弗蘭西斯·J·安德伍德  美國總統
那麼是奇幻小說嘍
So it's a fantasy novel.
這項法案從根本上
This is a fundamentally different look
重新審視了解決就業問題之道
at how to solve the problem of unemployment.
它有羅斯福新政的規模和深度
It has the size and the scope of the New Deal.
那麼說是社會主義的財富重新分配政策嘍
So it's a socialist redistribution of wealth
讓嬰兒潮一帶像七鰓鰻一樣吸住千禧一代
wherein the baby boomers will latch onto the millennials like a lamprey
分別指46年至65年出生的人和80年至00年出生的人
一直到把他們吸乾為止
and just keep sucking until they're as dry as a crouton?
這項法案旨在促進就業
This is about putting people to work
完全避免福利政策
and avoiding the entitlements entirely.
這我喜歡
Well, I like the sound of that.
怎麼  我們要讓私營公司經營社保
So what, we're gonna privatize Social Security
然後靠把老人趕盡殺絕提高稅收嗎
and then raise revenue by hunting the elderly for sport?
-好計劃  就這麼辦  -不  我說了
- Good plan. Use that. - No, as I said,
這是一種全新的方式
this is a fundamentally different approach entirely.
你覺得國會的
And you think that the Republicans
共和黨人會配合你嗎
in Congress will cooperate with you?
我想事實已經證明
Oh, I think that it has been proved
兩黨的心願是一致的
that both parties want the same thing.
2016年換個總統嗎
A new president in 2016?
不  我認為  徹底根除失業
No. No, I think actually, I think unemployment, eradicating it,
和強盛的經濟  是兩黨共同的願望
and I think a strong economy is something both parties want.
好吧  說到大家的心願
Okay, speaking of everyone,
路透社最近做了一項民調
there's a recent poll by Reuters.
我要說對了  結果顯示  十分之八的美國人
I wanna get this right. It says that eight out of ten Americans
都認為你  缺乏"效率和領導能力"
agree that you lack, quote, "Effectiveness and leadership."
聽我說  我不為這樣的民調操心
Uh, look, I don't let polls like that bother me.
我覺得等國人看到《美就法》執行
I think that once the nation sees AmWorks in action,
他們的態度就會轉變
they will change their attitudes.
什麼  "《美就法》"
I'm sorry, "AmWorks?"
抱歉  我還不知道是叫這麼個名字呢
I'm sorry-- I didn't realize it was called AmWorks.
聽著像安利啊  是傳銷嗎
Is that like Amway? Is it a pyramid scheme?
這就是你向美國人民兜售的嗎
Is that what you're selling the American people?
不  只是個縮略語  說起來方便
No, it's actually just an abbreviation to make it easier to say.
如果縮得夠小
Well, if you make it small enough,
或許嚥回去就更輕鬆了
uh, maybe it'll be easier to swallow.
要知道  雖然你是民主黨人  我還是尊重你
You know, even though you're a Democrat, I respect you.
但我們先看看事實
But let's just take a look at the facts here for a second.
你才做了六個月的總統
You've been president for six months,
我還是...要說對了
and again, I wanna get this right,
失業率上漲了
unemployment has gone up,
我們與中國的貿易逆差也上漲了
our trade deficit with China has increased,
否決數也大幅激增
the number of vetoes has skyrocketed.
我不太確信
I'm not entirely sure that I'm confident
你能像根除你的支持率那樣
that you'll be able to eradicate unemployment the same way
有效地根除失業
you've been able to eradicate your approval polls.
要知道...
What, you know, what do you--
你打算怎樣讓美國人民信服啊
How are you going to get it across to the American people?
道格
Doug?
賽斯
Seth?
嗯  是我
Yeah, it's me.
安德伍德夫人  她給了我這部手機...
Mrs. Underwood, she gave me this phone, but--
我知道  有什麼問題嗎
I know. Is something wrong?
沒有  我想找總統
No. I want to speak to the president.
急事嗎
Is it urgent?
我想跟他談《美國就業法案》的事
I want to talk to him about the America Works program.
那就不是急事嘍
So nothing urgent.
對  不緊急
It's not an emergency, no.
因為這電話是僅供緊急情況
'Cause that's what this phone is for.
你能轉達下我的請求嗎
Will you pass on my message?
你來遲了
You're late.
我換了三輛出租車
I switched cabs three times.
-你被人跟蹤了嗎  -不想抱僥倖心理
- Were you being followed? - Didn't want to take chances.
你知道我叫你來做什麼
You know why I asked you here.
我不知道她在哪
I don't know where she is.
那你就給我找到
Then you need to find out.
我查了她的社保號  名字
I ran her social, her name,
警方記錄  稅務記錄  都查了
police records, taxes, everything.
她說不定被哪個嫖客丟在陰溝裏了
She could be tossed in a ditch by a john for all I know.
-你在聯調局工作  -有我什麼好處
- You work at the FBI. - What do I get in return?
我的保護  如你所說
My protection, like you asked.
我以為你真有什麼  貨真價實的東西
I thought you had something to offer. Something real.
錢嗎
Like money?
比如幫我脫離聯調局
Like getting me out of the Bureau.
你實現這一點  我或許能幫你
You make that happen, maybe I can help you.
說好的條件是撤銷對你的指控
That was a condition, for your charges being dropped.
瞧  你現在沒人脈了
See, you don't still know people.
我就不該來
I shouldn't have even come here.
我是你唯一的安全保障
I am your only safety net.
你以為我會交出那些美國電話電報公司的記錄
You think I would have turned over all the AT&T records
而不給誰留個備份嗎
without leaving a backup with somebody?
我不會為了無用功報銷我的免牢金牌
I'm not gonna blow my get-out-of-jail card on a wild goose chase.
有人起疑嗎
Does anyone suspect anything?
聯調局那邊
At the Bureau?
沒人知道她
Nobody has a clue about her.
如果能讓你安心的話
If that gives you any peace of mind.
道格
Doug?
告訴他是急事
Tell him it's urgent.
我們希望能安排在五月
We're aiming for sometime in May.
我們一跟俄國代表團敲定日期
As soon as we agree on a date with the Russian delegation,
就馬上告訴你  格雷格
you will be the first to know. Uh, Greg.
與佩特羅夫在華盛頓的峰會
The Summit with Petrov here in Washington,
會談重點將是什麼
what'll be the focus of the talks?
對中東採取的雙邊政策
A bilateral approach to the Middle East.
你也知道  以色列軍隊不撤離約旦河谷
As you know, the Palestinians have refused to negotiate
巴勒斯坦就拒絕談判
until Israeli troops leave the Jordan Valley.
我們希望與佩特羅夫總統商議此事
We hope to address this with President Petrov
也好繼續談很多其他問題
so that we can move on to a whole host of other issues.
薩拉
Sara.
那麼這項政策的商議不包含以色列和巴勒斯坦
So this bilateral approach doesn't include Israel and Palestine.
國務院在向所有相關方做簡報
The State Department is briefing all interested parties.
峰會只是第一步  艾拉
The summit's really just a first step. Ayla.
我想就《美國就業法案》提問
I'd like to change course to the America Works program.
請問
Please.
我採訪了多位總統政策顧問
I've spoken to a number of the president's policy advisors,
他們說經濟團隊在這項就業計劃
who say there's been a lot of disagreement on the economic team
該採取何種形式方面有很多分歧
as to exactly what form this jobs package should take.
-哪些顧問  -想得美
- Which advisors? - Nice try.
我要說明  這並不僅僅是一項就業計劃
To be clear, this is far more than just a jobs package.
是一項全面的計劃
It is a comprehensive plan,
其目的是兩年內實現全面就業
which aims at full employment within two years.
就此而言  還有很多細節問題有待解決
So as such, there are a lot of details to be worked out.
所以你的消息來源不準確
So your sources are inaccurate.
並非是什麼分歧
It's not so much a disagreement
而是就計劃細節進行辯論  傑西
as it is debating the finer points of the plan. Jess.
我想再追問一句  都有些什麼細節問題
Just to follow up. What are some of the finer points?
甚至是計劃大致是如何
Or the broad strokes, even.
白宮沒有任何人透露任何信息
No one from the White House has said anything.
等我們能拿出計劃  我們就會拿出來
When we have a plan to present, we will present it.
傑西
Jess?
《美國就業法案》是否是
Is America Works a reaction
針對總統低支持率的舉措
to the president's low approval ratings?
為給競選造勢  而向民眾展現政績
An effort to offer some sign of progress ramping up to the elections?
我們從第一天就開始準備這項法案了
We've been working on this plan since day one.
這與支持率毫無關係
It has nothing to do with the approval ratings.
但至於選舉  今天該誰問了
But as for the election... uh, whose turn is it to ask today?
-馬克  -總統會參加2016年競選嗎
- Mark? - Is the president running in 2016?
今天  重點是好好執政  但是...
Today, the priority is good government, but...
明天接著問吧
Ask me again tomorrow.
謝謝大家
Thank you, everyone.
10點鐘有個空窗
We've got a window at ten.
我這就打給他
I'll call him now.
請坐
Please, sit down.
約翰  薩曼莎
John. Samantha.
你們跟記者說我們這屋裏出現的分歧了嗎
You spoke to a journalist about disagreements in this room?
再發生一次  你們就走人吧
If that happens again, you're off the team.
說到這屋裏出現的分歧
And speaking of the disagreements in this room,
我們現在出現了更大的分歧
we now have an even bigger one,
雷米給我看了你們目前的成果
because Remy has shown me your work so far and...
無力
it's toothless.
我三個月前站在這間屋子裏
I stood in this room three months ago
給你們下達了明確的指令
and gave you all very clear direction.
社會保險  醫療保險  醫療補助
Social Security, Medicare, Medicaid,
所有這些在吸乾國庫的福利項目
every entitlement program that is sucking us dry,
全都放在桌上
I want it all on the table.
這還遠遠不夠
And this doesn't go nearly far enough.
所以我們顯然是得回到一些基本問題上了
So we obviously have to get back to some basics.
回顧一些擺在我們面前的事實
Remind ourselves of some of the facts that are before us--
-先生  我能...  -不不不
- Sir, if I may-- - No, no, no, no.
我先說  然後你再說  保羅
I will speak first, and then you will speak, Paul.
這是國民一年平均從福利項目
This is what the average senior citizen gets,
得到的數額
one year from entitlements,
不管是清潔工  還是對沖基金經理
whether they were a janitor or they ran a hedge fund.
這筆錢  就是一份
That-- This money is a job
我們本可給一位單身母親
we could be giving to a single mother
或應屆畢業生的工作
or a student just out of school.
現在呢
Now, at the moment,
每一元的稅中有44美分流向了這些項目
44 cents of every tax dollar goes to pay for these programs.
到2030年  就將超過一半  62美分
By 2030, it'll be over half, 62 cents.
福利項目在讓國家破產
Entitlements are bankrupting us.
我讓雷米進行了一項民調
Now, I had Remy conduct a little poll.
提出陳述為  "做對國家有益的事
Statement posed was: "Doing what's best for my country
等於做我不喜歡的事"
means doing some things that I don't like."
74%的人認同這一陳述
Seventy-four percent agreed with this statement.
74%  這說明什麼
Seventy-four percent. Now, what does that tell us?
我們必須做人們不會喜歡的事
We have to do the things that people won't like.
即便我們做了
And even when we do,
也會有四分之三的人支持我們
three out of four of them will go along with us.
為什麼  因為我們能保證就業
And why? Because we're promising jobs.
再說一遍  我們要在哪三個領域
And again, where are the three areas
創造就業呢
that we're gonna be creating these jobs from?
州和聯邦基礎建設項目
Infrastructure at the state and federal level.
擴大軍隊
Increasing the size of the military,
並與私營部門合作
and working with our friends in the private sector to start--
抱歉  先生  我必須打斷
I'm sorry, sir, but I have to interrupt.
你要削減或砍掉的項目
The programs that you want to scale back or dismantle
是美國夢的基石啊
are the bedrock of the American dream.
工作努力  交稅
You work hard, you pay your taxes--
不  抱歉  那曾是美國夢的基石
No, I'm sorry, they were the bedrock of the American dream.
但現在不是了
But they're not anymore.
尤其是對那失業的一千萬人來說
Certainly not for the ten million people who are out of work.
但從實際角度出發  數千特殊利益群體
But practically speaking, a thousand special interests,
工會  兩黨都有反對聲音
organized labor, opposition in both parties.
我們可以就你的提議折中一下...
Now, we can do a version of what you're proposing--
我不要折中
I don't want a version.
我要遠大願景
I want a vision.
作為團隊領袖  我認為我可以代表所有人說
As head of this team, and I think I speak for everyone,
-我們已經...  -作為總統
- we have done-- - Speaking as the president,
我選擇了這支團隊  你們為我工作
who chose this team and for whom it works,
我要拿到五千億美元
I want five hundred billion dollars
給一千萬民眾工作
to put ten million people to work.
我不管這多讓人肉疼
I don't care how much it hurts.
我不管這有多具爭議性
I don't care how controversial it is.
你們的職責  就是找出辦法
Your job is to find a way.
說服國會和美國人民是我的工作
It's my job to convince Congress and the American people.
你們的工作不是向我推銷你們的妥協方案
Your job is not to sell me on your version of my program.
大家都清楚自己該做什麼了嗎
Now, are we all clear on what our jobs are?
很好  因為我要在30天內
Good, because I want to present this proposal
向領導層呈遞這份提議
to leadership in 30 days.
-我們實現這個目標吧  -保羅
- Let's make it happen. - Paul?
-我們不再需要你了  -什麼
- Your services are no longer needed. - Excuse me?
別聲張  保持和氣
Let's keep it quiet, let's keep it cordial.
-多謝你的辛勞  -我去收拾東西
- Thanks for all your work. - I'll get my things.
我會叫人給你送到大廳的
I'll have them sent down to you in the lobby.
喂
Hello?
好的  馬上就來
Yeah. I'm on my way.
天啊
God!
請您稍等幾分鐘  請坐
It'll be a few minutes. Please, have a seat.
-你知道多久了  -兩個月
- How long have you known? - Two months.
我作為法官的能力尚未受到影響
It hasn't impaired my judgment on the bench.
而且目前只是早期
And it's early on.
還要一段時間才會有一些明顯的癥狀
We don't expect any real symptoms for quite some time.
暫時我還不會穿著
I won't be wandering around the Supreme Court
短褲在最高法院亂晃
in my boxer shorts anytime soon.
但是我想現在就趁早退休  別到那一步
But I'd like to retire now, long before we get there.
大法官  我非常感謝你能有勇氣來
Well, Justice, I want to thank you for having the courage
告知我這個消息
to come and share this news with me.
你確定診斷無誤嗎
Are you sure the diagnosis is correct?
我的醫生就是給副總統夫人看病的那位
My doctor's the same that treated the Vice President's wife.
他是美國最厲害的老年癡呆專家
He's the foremost Alzheimer's specialist in America.
是的  我任命唐納德為副總統了
Yes, I made Donald my vice president.
與其讓他在國會惹事  不如放在身邊
I'd rather him be a pain in my ass here than over in Congress.
而且就算是共和黨員
And even the Republicans
也不能拒絕剛剛經歷喪妻之痛的人
couldn't refuse a man who just buried his wife.
瑪喬莉走得這麼快真是可怕
Terrible how quickly Marjory went.
我現在就告訴你
I'm telling you this now
這樣你就有時間考慮一下人選
so you have time to think about candidates
然後我再宣佈退休
before I announce my retirement.
-你能給我多長時間  -你需要多長時間
- How much time can you give me? - How much do you need?
我正要向國會提出《美國就業法案》
I'm about to introduce America Works to Congress.
肯定不會輕鬆
It's sure to be an uphill battle.
還是不要再加個最高法院法官提名來添亂了
And I'd prefer not to add a Supreme Court nomination to the mix.
共和黨肯定會拿這個當籌碼
The Republicans will just use it as leverage.
我聽到了一些風聲  要拿福利開刀嗎
I've heard rumblings. Entitlements on the chopping block?
所以更需要你繼續坐鎮
All the more reason to keep you on the bench.
司法部肯定會提出異議
It's sure to be challenged in the Judiciary.
總統先生  我想和我妻子
Mr. President, I want to spend as much time
盡量多在一起
with my wife as possible
趁著我這兩年還清醒
in the good years that I have left.
瑪喬莉確診的時候  她也是這麼想的
When Marjory was ill, she wanted the same thing.
她離開了史密森尼學會  但是你知道嗎
She left the Smithsonian, and you know what?
她在家每一秒都很煩躁  因為不能做事了
She hated every second of being at home, of not being productive,
不能從事自己熱愛的事業
of not doing what she loved.
她那段時間過得很艱難
It made her time with us much harder, and...
也非常不開心
it made her deeply unhappy.
工作是最好的調劑  我真希望她當時沒退休
Work is the best distraction. I wish she hadn't retired.
而且  她頭腦還清楚的時候
And, uh... before she lost her lucid thought,
她說她也很後悔
she said she regretted it, too.
能不能再堅持六個月  最多一年
Can you give me six months? A year at the most? That's all.
讓我在應付最高法院的爭鬥之前
Just enough time to get this program up and running
能有時間讓這個法案順利開展
before I have to face a Supreme Court fight.
-我得考慮考慮  -當然
- I need to think it over. - Oh, of course.
-和你夫人商量一下  -我送你出去
- Speak to your wife. - I'll walk you out.
-研究中心盡快給我落實  -說話算話
- I better get that research center. - Yes, a deal is a deal.
上帝啊  唐納德  咱們趕緊幹活兒吧
Now, good God, Donald, let's get something done.
現在你知道為什麼唐納德會同意了
Now you see why Donald said yes.
他雖恨我入骨
He may hate my guts,
但是再沒什麼比家庭成員去世
but there's nothing like a death in the family
更能讓人識時務了
to separate the wheat from the bullshit.
讓他進來吧
Send him in.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
總統可以見你了
The president is ready to see you now.
道格
Doug.
總統先生
Mr. President.
醫生告訴我你恢復得很好
The doctor told me your recovery is going very well.
是啊  就是要用這個
Yeah. Well, there's this.
別的地方都恢復如初
But everything else is as good as new.
見到你真是太好了
It's great to see you.
克萊爾和我擔心得要死
Claire and I have been worried sick about you.
謝謝你們的禮物
Thank you for the gifts.
也謝謝你們的照顧
For looking out for me.
我沒多少親密的朋友  你是其中之一
I don't have that many close friends. I count you among them.
我很感激你這麼說  先生
I appreciate your saying that, sir.
別叫我先生  我們是老朋友了
Oh, drop the "Sir." We're old pals.
嗯
Well...
我才應該道歉
I'm the one who should apologize.
你又給了我個機會  你相信我
You gave me another chance. You trusted me.
這一切我一人承擔
And what happened, I take responsibility for that.
讓你陷入那種處境
No, for putting you in that position.
別  沒這必要
Stop. It's not necessary.
-我讓你身陷危機  -沒錯  但我只在乎
- I endangered you just as-- - Yeah, but all I care about
你還活著  在逐漸恢復
is that you are alive and getting better.
其它的都過去吧
Let the rest of it go.
-你知道我多忠心  -這不用你說
- You know how devoted I am. - You don't have to say it.
你一次又一次地證明了自己
You proved it time and time again.
來  坐下
Now, come on, come on, sit down.
坐在這兒
Right here.
當初有機會時我就該解決了她
I should've taken care of her when I had the chance.
我還沒找到她
I haven't found her yet.
等我找到她  一定確保別人再找不到
But when I do, I'll make sure that no one else does.
我向你保證  先生
You can count on that, sir.
你打算怎麼辦...
How is it, uh...?
我不告訴你可能比較好
Probably better if we don't talk about it.
嗯  是啊
Right, of course.
他們說你要見我
Well, they told me you needed to see me.
先生  我知道這要求很過分
Well, sir, I... I know that it's a lot to ask,
我給我們惹了這麼大麻煩
and that I probably don't deserve it,
我或許也不配
considering the mess I put us in.
你肯定也有顧慮
And I'm sure you have your doubts.
我知道我不能明目張膽  但...
I realize it couldn't be anything too visible, but...
我一直在跟進《美國就業法案》的報道
I've been following everything with America Works.
這扯哪去了
Well, that's a ways off.
我覺得我能幫上忙
But I was thinking that I could help.
遊說委員會領導層應該有明確目標
There should be a targeted plan for lobbying committee leadership.
我能配合政治團隊
And I can work with the political team,
協調國會立法主任和幕僚長
coordinate with House leg directors, chiefs of staff--
我昨天去了加夫尼給我父親掃墓
I was in Gaffney yesterday, visiting my father's grave.
他從不好好照顧自己
He never took care of himself.
不顧自己心臟有病  最終付出代價
He ignored his heart problems and... he paid the price.
你得尊重自己終有一死的命運  道格
You have to respect your own mortality, Doug.
我不想給你收屍
I don't want to be standing over your grave.
告訴你...
Now, look...
我保證你在這裏會有一席之地
There is a place for you here, I promise.
但心急吃不了熱豆腐
But we have to go about this slowly.
我在家工作  只跟你和雷米直接接觸
I'll work from home. Only direct contact with you or Remy.
要知道你幫我的最好辦法
You know the way that you can help me the best
就是好好恢復身體
is to do exactly what you're doing right now,
不要分心
focusing on your recovery.
如果我操之過急
I would never forgive myself
讓你壓力太大  我絕不會原諒自己
if I put too much on your plate too soon.
沒錯
You're right.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
謝謝
Thank you.
抱歉  我得走了
I'm sorry, I have to go.
但我說的都是真心話
But look, I meant what I said.
等你準備好了再說
When you are truly ready.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
你想待多久待多久
Stay as long as you like.
三小時前  我們定位到
Three hours ago, we pinpointed him here,
他在也門的夏卜瓦省
in the Shabwa region of Yemen.
配合方面呢
Cooperation?
我幾分鐘前和外交部長談過
I spoke to the foreign minister a few minutes ago.
-有多少平民  -二十幾個  不明身份
- Civilians? - Two dozen, non-IDs.
太多了
That's too many.
我們擔心他可能隨時離開
Our concern is that he could be on the move at any moment.
先生  鑒於佩特羅夫要來華盛頓...
Sir, with Petrov coming to Washington--
我們花了兩年才找到阿卜杜拉
It's taken us two years to track Abdullah down.
不能為了峰會就放棄一切機會
We can't ignore every opportunity between now and the summit.
你們看到村子情況了嗎
Do you have eyes on the village?
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
他就在這棟房子裏
He's in this building here.
50米內不留活口
Kill zone is anyone within 50 meters.
如果沒有平民傷亡就能除掉他
If we take him out with no civilian casualties,
我就同意這次襲擊
I'll authorize the strike.
先生  恕我冒昧  我真心認為
Sir, if I may, I really think--
還有不到兩個月佩特羅夫總統就將來訪華盛頓
President Petrov is coming to Washington in less than two months.
我們整個中東政策都靠這次峰會
Our entire Middle East policy hinges on that meeting.
如果可能  我們不想給穆斯林社會任何
We don't want to give the Muslim community any viable reasons
阻撓進程的借口
to obstruct things if we can avoid it.
想辦法不殺死平民就除掉他
So find a way to do this without killing civilians.
非常感謝各位
Thank you all very much.
能單獨談會兒嗎  是克萊爾的事
May I have a moment? It's about Claire.
如果你丈夫提名你  我不會手下留情的
If your husband nominates you, I can't pull any punches.
沒經驗  任人唯親
Lack of experience. Nepotism.
沒錯
That's right.
你覺得我太業餘
And you think I'm a dilettante.
不  但很多人會這麼認為
No. But plenty of people will.
打從弗蘭西斯一就職我就在準備了
I've been preparing since Francis took office.
經驗的缺乏我會用職業道德補上
What I lack in experience I'll make up for in work ethic.
為什麼要當聯合國大使
Why Ambassador to the UN?
你作為第一夫人有更大的影響力
You wield far more influence as the First Lady.
那和切實地去做貢獻不一樣
That's not the same as contributing in a concrete way.
如果我們投票否決了你
If we vote down your confirmation,
你能接受在公眾面前丟面子嗎
are you comfortable with that sort of public embarrassment?
我知道有這風險
I know that's a risk.
-你2016年會競選吧  -無可奉告
- You're running in 2016, right? - No comment.
弗蘭西斯和我都驚訝於
Francis and I are impressed
共和黨人如此支持你
by how the Republicans are consolidating around you.
你會是一個優秀的候選人
You'll make a good candidate.
但不能和總統夫人勾結
Not by linking arms with the president's wife.
如果我搞砸了  這會是有力的競選廣告
If I'm a disaster, it makes for a good campaign ad.
如果我做得好  那你更是無可指摘
If I do a good job, nobody can fault you.
無論如何這都不會影響你2016的競選
Either way, it doesn't hurt your chances in 2016.
我很感激你在公佈消息前先來找我
Well, I appreciate you coming by before going public.
很有風度也很周到
It is classy, and thoughtful.
我不會故意阻礙你的
I won't actively block you.
剩下就靠你自己努力了
The rest is on your shoulders.
謝謝  參議員
Thank you, Senator.
告訴總統我這麼做是出於對你的敬意
Tell the president I'm doing this out of respect to you.
我在普選上打敗弗蘭克前  他都會在我黑名單上
Frank's still on my shit list till I beat him in the general.
好的
I will.
你怎麼不立刻過來
Why didn't you come right away?
我有個會面不能錯過
I had a meeting I couldn't miss.
該死的華盛頓
Fucking Washington.
-會有些疼  -我知道
- This is gonna hurt. - I know.
這是撲熱息痛  能止痛
Here's some Percocet. It'll help with the pain.
我給你開個30天的處方
I'll write you a 30-day prescription.
我不能
I can't.
-我不能...  -什麼
- I'm not supposed to-- - What was that?
沒事
Nothing.
好了  你可以走了
All right. You're good to go.
-和門多薩談得如何  -我覺得還不錯
- How did it go with Mendoza? - Well, I think.
他會支持你嗎
He'll support you?
他不會公開反對
He won't openly fight it.
那可以一大進步
Well, that is a big step forward.
-道格說了什麼  -沒什麼新消息
- How did it go with Doug? - No real news.
你今晚還要在這裏睡嗎
Hey, are you in here again tonight?
我感冒還沒好  不想傳染給你
I'm still getting over this cold. I don't want to get you sick.
好吧  別做事做得太晚了
Well, don't stay up with all that too late.
弗蘭西斯
Francis?
我們什麼時候公佈提名
When do we announce the nomination?
聽著  我今晚本來不想談這事
Listen, I wasn't gonna bring this up tonight,
可你得知道國務院那邊
but you should know that there are some serious doubts
有很多疑慮
from people at the State Department.
你是說凱茜
You mean Cathy.
還有她的一些手下
And some on her staff.
什麼樣的疑慮
Like what?
就是"能力不足""身兼兩職"之類的
Well, in over your head, wearing two hats, the obvious things.
你是不是不想這麼做了才這麼說
And are you saying this because you don't want to move forward?
當然不是  我告訴你  是希望你完全明白
Not at all. I'm sharing with you so you fully understand
你要面對的情況
what you're getting into.
我明白
And I do.
或許我們不該著急
Maybe we shouldn't rush this.
-你現在也有疑慮了  -我可沒這麼說
- You're having doubts now, too. - I didn't say that.
只是你該多考慮考慮這麼做
Only you should put more thought into whether
是否對你合適  就是這樣
this is the right move for you. That's all.
晚安  弗蘭西斯
Good night, Francis.
早日康復
Feel better.
弗蘭西斯
Francis.
我想你這周宣佈提名的消息
I want you to announce the nomination this week.
我不想等了  沒有什麼好時機
I don't want to wait. The timing will never be good.
我明明能積攢實戰經驗
And I don't want to waste time
何必要浪費時間呢
when I can be getting real experience under my belt.
定個日子舉辦新聞發佈會吧
So set a date, hold a press conference, and let's do it.
克萊爾
Claire!
我提到凱茜並不是說我認為
I was not trying to suggest that you not be the ambassador
你不該當大使  我只是...
when I brought up Cathy. I was just--
我們早說好了
We made a deal,
現在你卻要食言了
and now you're trying to back away from it.
-不是這樣的  -那你就會告訴凱茜
- That is not true. - Then you would've told Cathy
事情就是這樣  讓她接受
it's happening to make her peace with that.
-沒那麼簡單  -就是那麼簡單
- It's not that simple. - Yes, it is.
-你是總統  -我不能控制國會
- You're the president. - I can't control Congress.
我想啟動兩項重要項目
I'm trying to get two major initiatives off the ground
我的每一步行動都將產生影響
and every move I make will have an effect.
我們早在走進白宮之前就已經說定了
We agreed to this before we ever stepped foot in this house.
-我知道我們說定了  -如果我沒有
- I know what we agreed to. - How am I supposed to run for office
令人信服的資歷  日後我怎麼競選總統
at some point if I don't have a legitimate track record?
我們必須撐過接下來這18個月
We have to survive the next 18 months,
取得點成績  再說後面的事
accomplish something, and then look ahead.
弗蘭西斯  我們還是現實一點
Francis, let's be realistic.
你能否當選總統完全是沒準的事
There's no guarantee you'll get elected.
如果你落選  我得有所準備
I need to be prepared if you don't.
你對我還真是有信心啊
You have that much faith in me, do you?
看來比你對我的信心要大
More faith than you have in me, it seems.
我相信你勝過任何人  克萊爾
I believe in you more than anyone, Claire.
那表現出來  提名我
Then show it. Nominate me.
別讓我再費口舌說服你
I shouldn't have to convince you.
不是說不說服的事
It's not about convincing.
而是我們得看清當下的政治氣候
It's about being honest about the political climate
-我們現在的處境  -我快要年過半百了
- that we find ourselves-- - I'm almost 50 years old.
幾十年來我一直當你的賢內助
I've been in the passenger seat for decades.
也該讓我自主一回了
It's time for me to get behind the wheel.
必須現在就開始著手  趕在大選之前
That needs to start now. Before the election.
因為誰知道那時會發生什麼
Because who knows what will happen?
萬一你輸了呢
What if you lose?
我不會只當個填座總統的  克萊爾
I will not be a placeholder president, Claire.
我一定會贏  我會名垂青史
I will win. And I will leave a legacy.
你是說我們會名垂青史
You mean we will.
打擾了  先生
Excuse me, sir.
國防部長來電  他說有要事
The Secretary of Defense is on the line. He says it's urgent.
什麼事
Yes?
好的
Okay.
我這就去
I'm coming.
等我到了再開始
Not until I get there.
-我馬上下去  -好的  先生
- I'll be right down. - Yes, sir.
穿好衣服  我有東西要給你看
Get dressed. I want you to see something.
進來
Come in.
-給  -多謝
- Here. - Thank you.
那好
Okay, great.
去脫吧
Get undressed.
這是怎麼回事
How did this happen?
不重要
Doesn't matter.
我來幫你
Let me help you.
讓我來
I'll... I'll do it.
我會小心的
I'll be gentle.
不用小心
Don't be gentle.
像這樣嗎
Like that?
沒錯
Yeah.
-搞什麼鬼  -是波本
- What the fuck? - It's bourbon.
-我  -隻是波本而已
- I-- - That's all. It's just bourbon.
-拿著  -我真不想
- Take it. - I really don't want to.
不是用來注射的
Nothing's going through the skin.
我只是想讓你
I just want you to squirt it...
把酒射進我嘴裏
into my mouth.
好嗎  拜託了
Okay? Please.
-那是目標嗎  -是的  先生
- Is that our target? - Yes, sir.
總統先生  這次行動是高度機密
Mr. President, this is a highly classified operation--
我授權第一夫人在場旁觀行動
I'm clearing the First Lady for this operation.
好的  請原諒  先生
Yes, sir. Forgive me, sir.
隨時準備發射  先生
We are armed and ready, sir.
阿卜杜拉就在那些車輛中
Abdullah is in one of those vehicles.
具體哪一輛我們還不清楚
We can't tell which one.
如果他們兵分三路行動的話
If they go in three different directions,
我們將不知道該摧毀哪一路
we wouldn't know where to strike,
如果讓他逃回山中
and if he makes it back to the mountains,
我們的衛星就追蹤不到他了
we'll lose our satellite track on him.
那些是孩子嗎
Are those children?
我不能確定  先生  但有這個可能
I can't say definitely, sir, but they could be.
可以發動打擊嗎  先生
Do we have authorization, sir?
-行動吧  -執行打擊
- Proceed. - Proceed with the launch.
倒計時10秒
And ten seconds.
5  4  3
And five, four, three...
目標已摧毀  先生
Target is destroyed, sir.
謝謝各位
Thank you, everyone.
我還是要提名
I still want it.
那好吧
All right.
2011年夏天  美國總統奧巴馬同國會就"債務上限"展開激烈爭鬥
在談判中最終敗給國會新當選的一批共和黨保守派"茶黨"的議員
共和黨取得了談判勝利
"債務上限"一役使奧巴馬民望大跌  不僅反對派共和黨對他不以為然
民主黨內也有很多人認為他缺乏領導能力
為挽回民望和政治影響力
奧巴馬於2011年9月8日在國會發表全國性講話
鄭重推出《美國工作法案》(American Jobs Act)
該法案擬在不增加預算赤字的情況下
通過不同渠道籌款四千四百七十億美元  用於創造就業
然而該法案推出後  不僅遭到國會共和黨的強烈反對
在民主黨佔多數的參議院也沒得到足夠的支持
由於無法在國會得到通過  白宮被迫將這個法案分拆成幾個小法案
但是即使委曲求全  分拆後的法案也大都沒通過
如需其它字幕  請登陸新浪微博[WEB&BD版美劇字幕精編者]
或發郵件 lj20090303@163.com